hawtcelebs.com 2019-12-04

# Privacy Policy – HawtCelebs

Hawtcelebs has created this privacy statement to describe our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: “hawtcelebs.com” at [http://www.hawtcelebs.com](https://www.hawtcelebs.com/).  We seek to protect your private information so that you have a pleasurable viewing experience on our Web site. We will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone except as explained in this policy. Please return to this page from time to time, as we will be updating this statement as our services continue to grow. We welcome and encourage questions, comments, and suggestions. Please contact us at a.arsenovic.sg[at]gmail.com with any questions. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies store information about your use of a particular Web site or service and are typically used to make services more convenient and personalized. Most cookies are “session cookies,” which are automatically deleted whenever you leave a Web site, although some cookies remain on your computer until you remove them. 

## Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser(s) may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

## How We Use Cookies

We use cookies 

  * (1) to estimate the number of visitors to our Web site
  * (2) to measure general traffic patterns, and
  * (3) to personalize information and services we provide to you on the site.

Companies that place ads on the hawtcelebs.com Web site may also use their own cookies to help determine the frequency and placement of particular ads. Your browser controls how cookies are used and can be set to not allow them. However, it is possible that some parts of the hawtcelebs.com site may not function properly if your browser refuses our cookies. We may, from time to time, use cookies to store your zip code and email address for use with certain current or future services such as e-mail update list(s), showtimes e-mail services, local showtimes profiles, theater and movie preference profiles. 

## Cookie Notification and Disabling

You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish – for details, see [aboutcookies.org](http://aboutcookies.org/). You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work. 

## Personally Identifiable Information

**What Personally Identifiable Information Is** Personally identifiable information is your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card information. 

## Where We Collect Personally Identifiable Information

hawtcelebs.com collects personally identifiable information when you (1) subscribe to our mailing list(s), (2) enter contests, (3) buy products, make referrals, or use the “tell a friend” option, and (4) submit feedback, questions, or “contact us” messages. 

## How We Use Personally Identifiable Information

hawtcelebs.com uses your personally identifiable information to personalize your experience on our Web site, to deliver products and/or services ordered and/or purchased by you and to contact you. Hawtcelebs.com also compiles aggregate data from all of our customers to prepare internal reports about which pages are popular, how many total unique users visit our site, and different traffic patterns. Hawtcelebs.com does not combine your personally identifiable information with information about pages visited, purchases made, or any other click-stream data. 

## Who We Disclose Personally Identifiable Information To

hawtcelebs.com will not sell, rent, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone except as explained in this policy. hawtcelebs.com may disclose some personal information to outside companies who help hawtcelebs.com with the administration and delivery of newsletters, promotional games, trivia contests, and sweepstakes. For example, a company who administers a sweepstakes for us may use your e-mail address to update you on your status in the sweepstakes. Or, our newsletters may be distributed by another company that will use your e-mail or shipping address for delivery. The hawtcelebs.com Web site contains links to other Web sites. Although we do not provide any personally identifiable information to these companies, we cannot guarantee your privacy once you leave thehawtcelebs.com Web site.hawtcelebs.com is not responsible for the privacy policies, practices, or content of Web sites with links on our site. hawtcelebs.com may also disclose your personal information to law enforcement personnel, government officials, or others when we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is necessary to prevent violations of the law, injury to person or property, or any harm to hawtcelebs.com or others. 

## Communication

We collect personally identifiable information such as first and last name and email address when you sign up for our email list(s). These email services provide hawtcelebs.com users free opt-in updates about thehawtcelebs.com site and movie information and/or content. We may also request secondary information, such as your movie preferences, which we will use to help personalize the site for you in the future. We may also on occasion send promotional and informational mail to you from hawtcelebs.com. You may opt-out of receiving these secondary communications by sending an email with “remove” in the subject line to a.arsenovic.sg[at]gmail.com . 

## Demographic Information

Demographic information may be collected on the web site. The information will only be shared with any third-parties in an aggregate format. 

## Public Forums

This site makes voting and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal opinion. Personally identifiable information is not made available to the public or to other users and voting is anonymous. However, when using message boards, your user name and email address – which constitutes personally identifiable information, provided by you, is made available on the message boards. 

## Log Files

hawtcelebs.com, both using its own systems and the systems of others (such as Google or Quantcast, among others) automatically logs information such as IP addresses, ISPs, and browser type but does not link that information to personally identifying information. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

## Sharing of Information

hawtcelebs.com is engaged in “powered by” relationships as more fully described herein. hawtcelebs.com does not share any personally identifiable information with third-parties, other than its partners as herein described, and will otherwise only share information in aggregate form. We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies from banner ads are collected by advertising networks, and we do not have access to this information. 

## Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

## Third-parties and Opt-Out

Third-parties may display interest-based advertising to you in applications or websites, based on your use of applications or websites over time and across non-affiliated apps. Such third-parties may combine and use information from websites or applications on your current browser or device with information from your other browsers or devices for advertising purposes. To opt-out of such interest-based advertising and/or cross-device targeting, please use the methods provided below for opting out on each of your browsers and on each of your devices: Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) – <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/> Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) – <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> Digital Advertising Alliance Canada (DAAC) – <http://youradchoices.ca/choices> Digital Advertising Alliance EU (EDAA) – <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/> Please note that opting out of interest-based advertising and cross-device targeting does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. It does mean that the third-party from which you have opted out of receiving interest-based advertising or cross-device targeting by using the methods provided above will no longer deliver ads tailored to your Web preferences and usage patterns on a particular web browser or device. 

## Disclosure Regarding Google Display Advertising

We implement Google Analytics features that use Display Advertising information for Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising, to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, by going to the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). We, along with third-party vendors (including Google), use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookies) to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our website. You can read more about the cookies  used by Google Analytics advertising features, by going to the [Google Analytics Privacy Policy page](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). 

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Employees are notified in staff meetings of security policies and practices regularly. Access to data limited and employees obtain access to log files by a secured password. hawtcelebs periodically reviews web security and ensures that all policies and practices are adhered to within the company. 

## Children

**Our Policy For Guests Under Age 18** hawtcelebs.com is committed to protecting the privacy of children. We encourage parents and guardians to explore the Internet with their children. Visitors under age 18 should not submit any personally identifiable information to hawtcelebs.com. 

## Links

hawtcelebs.com site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are ‘clicking’ to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours. 

## Correct/Update or Cancel Subscription

Users can change their information with hawtcelebs.com by emailing a request to a.arsenovic.sg[at]gmail.com . If you wish to unsubscribe from any hawtcelebs mailing list, please email a.arsenovic.sg[at]gmail.com using the e-mail address you would like removed and type “UNSUBSCRIBE” as the subject of the message. 

## Notification of Changes

hawtcelebs.com privacy practices may change periodically. hawtcelebs.com will notify users of changes only if the information collected from the user differs from that stated at the time of collection. hawtcelebs.com may also obtain the user’s consent by posting notice on the site. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact hawtcelebs:  Email: a.arsenovic.sg[at]gmail.com
